[BOLLYWOOD FILM PLAYING ON TV]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Raj:)It's open.
(Howard:)Hey, pal.
(Raj:)What do you want?
(Howard:)I brought you a little gift.
(Howard:)New kite.
(Raj:)The kite you made me lose
was an authentic Patang.
An Indian kite my brother sent
to me from New Delhi.
(Raj:)It took me a day to put together
and two days to paint.
(Raj:)This is Hello Kitty.
(Howard:)Yeah, but it comes
with a little coin purse.
(Howard:)Does a Patang?
(Raj:)Wow, you just don't get it, do you?
Buying me something pretty isn't gonna
make our problem just go away.
(Howard:)Look, I admit I haven't always been
the best friend I could be.
(Raj:)You've been a sucky friend.
A sucky, sucky friend.
(Howard:)-Stipulated.
-And you do it all the time.
Last week, we were looking for a phone
with giant numbers for your mother...